

Tyler Davies

+1 (951) 288-1154 www.TylerDavies.org

SUMMARY

contact@TylerDavies.org | +1 (951) 288-1154

I'm an Information Technology graduate and Full Stack Developer student with approximately 15 years using and working with computer operating systems, over 10 years of tinkering with computer components and building workstation and gaming computers, and 4 years of undergrad studies related to computer hardware, networking infrastructure, programming, and project management.

I've built every desktop workstation I've ever owned, dabbling heavily in game and web design while also learning a number of programming languages such as Java, HTML, CSS, JS, C#, Python and the React.js framework.

SKILLS

- Access Point Configuration
- Break-Fix
- Ticketing Software
- Hardware Troubleshooting and Repair
- Device/Hardware QA
- UI/UX
- Figma

- Software Installation and Configuration
- Customer Service
- Network Configuration
- Hardware Configuration
- Agile Methodology and Scrum
- Virtualization (Hyper-V)
- Firewall Configuration

- C#, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, React, Node, Electron
- Visual Studio & VSCode
- Github
- Microsoft Office
- Google Suite
- Windows & MacOS
- Software Development

WORK HISTORY

IT Technician II / Software Developer- Apple, Mesa, AZ

01/2024 - Current

- $\circ\,$ Configuration and QA of routers, switches, printers, scanners, desktop computers, laptops, and more
- Developing internal software to automate configuration tasks, improving efficiency and consistency
- $\circ\,$ Writing documentation on how to perform job duties as well as how to use software I've developed or helped to develop

Service Assistant - Costco Wholesale, Sheridan, CO

Bakery, merchandising, cashier assistant, inventory, customer service

10/2021 - 07/2022

IT / Help Desk / Administrative Assistant - Fantastic Displays, Riverside, CA

Fixing computer and network issues, replacing peripherals, recording inventory, running CAT throughout office space, setting up network switching, product QA, customer assistance, product sourcing, shipping/receiving, other miscellaneous tasks

06/2019 - 04/2020

Team Leader - Harkins Theatres, Moreno Valley, CA

Managing schedules and duties of team members, ensuring theaters are cleaned, keeping concessions running smoothly, and handling customer concerns and questions

02/2017 - 06/2019

EDUCATION

Information Technology - Bachelor's of Science - University of Phoenix - Nov 2023

Full Stack Development - Certificate - Codecademy - In Progress

Computer Programming Logic - Certificate - University of Phoenix - Aug 2023